<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Sushant</title>
    <link>http://sushantdhiman.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Sushant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>map[host:outlook.com username:sushantdhiman] (Sushant)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>map[host:outlook.com username:sushantdhiman] (Sushant)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sushantdhiman.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Price</title>
      <link>http://sushantdhiman.com/blog/price/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>map[host:outlook.com username:sushantdhiman] (Sushant)</author>
      <guid>http://sushantdhiman.com/blog/price/</guid>
      <description>Yet another short story, I remembered this evening.
The Story Once there was a teacher who used to make mud toys. He also had one student, who was learning this art from him. Both used to make mud toys and sell them in market. This is how they made their living.
There was an interesting thing about this student teacher pair. Every toy that teacher used to sell was priced at ₹5, on other hand toys made by his student used to fetch much more price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diminishing capability</title>
      <link>http://sushantdhiman.com/blog/diminishing-capability/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>map[host:outlook.com username:sushantdhiman] (Sushant)</author>
      <guid>http://sushantdhiman.com/blog/diminishing-capability/</guid>
      <description>With advancement in technology humans have achieved so much. Technology took us to the moon, now we are pushing further into space. Destinations which used to take many days to reach, now can be covered in matter of hours.
Most important advancement has been in the field of communication, If some important incident happens in USA, I will usually hear about it in news, even though there is 12 hour timezone gap.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parable of Onion</title>
      <link>http://sushantdhiman.com/blog/parabel-of-onion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>map[host:outlook.com username:sushantdhiman] (Sushant)</author>
      <guid>http://sushantdhiman.com/blog/parabel-of-onion/</guid>
      <description>Let talk about something spiritual. While browsing Reddit the other day I found a very interesting story that I would definitely like to share. This story is called the Parable of the Onion.
The Story Once upon a time there was an old woman who had died and found herself in hell. She complained to Satan that her assignment to the netherworld was a mistake.
Satan told her, “You’ve been a greedy, selfish woman all your life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>